Goodson, William Wilson, Jr., collector. Science fiction fanzines and related papers collected by William Wilson Goodson Jr., 1970-2008 (SF-3136): PRELIMINARY BOX LIST.
William Wilson Goodson Jr. collection of science fiction fanzines and related papers,
- I. Science fiction fanzines
  - Ti - Tm
    - Tightbeam: number 194; 1995 July. (box 4)
    - Tightbeam: number 195; 1995 September. (box 4)
    - Tightbeam: number 196; 1995 November. (box 4)
    - Tightbeam: number 197; 1996 January. (box 4)
    - Tightbeam: number 198; 1996 March. (box 4)
    - Tightbeam: number 199; 1996 May. (box 4)
    - Tightbeam: number 200; 1996 July. (box 4)
    - Tightbeam: number 201; 1996 September. (box 4)
    - Tightbeam: number 202; 1996 November. (box 4)
    - Tightbeam: number 203; 1997 January. (box 4)
    - Tightbeam: number 204; 1997 March. (box 4)
    - Tightbeam: number 205; 1997 May. (box 4)
    - Tightbeam: number 206; 1997 July. (box 4)
    - Tightbeam: number 207; 1997 September. (box 4)
    - Tightbeam: number 208; 1997 November. (box 4)
    - Tightbeam: number 209; 1998 January. (box 4)
    - Tightbeam: number 221; 2000 January. (box 4)
    - Tightbeam: number 224; 2000 August. (box 4)
    - Tightbeam Newsletter for TNFF: number 29; 1981 January. (box 3)
      Editor: Lynne Holdom.
    - Tightbeam Newsletter for TNFF: number 30; 1981 May. (box 3)
    - Tightbeam Newsletter for TNFF: number 121; 1981 September. (box 3)
    - Tightbeam Newsletter for TNFF: number 130; 1983 Winter. (box 3)
      Editor: Owen K. Laurion.
    - Tightbeam Newsletter for TNFF: number 131; 1984 April. (box 3)
    - Tightbeam Newsletter for TNFF: number 132; 1984 June. (box 3)
    - Tightbeam Newsletter for TNFF: number 158; 1989 March. (box 3)
      Editor: Ingrid Maakk.
    - Tightbeam Newsletter for TNFF: number 159; 1989 May. (box 3)
    - Tightbeam Newsletter for TNFF: number 161; 1989 December. (box 3)
    - Tightbeam Newsletter for TNFF: number 163; 1990. (box 3)
    - Tightbeam Newsletter for TNFF: number 168; 1990 March. (box 3)
    - Tightbeam Newsletter for TNFF: number 174; 1992 March. (box 3)
    - Tightbeam Newsletter for TNFF: number 175; 1992 May. (box 3)
    - Tightbeam Newsletter for TNFF: number 176; 1992 July. (box 3)
    - Tightbeam Newsletter for TNFF: number 179; 1993 January. (box 3)
    - Tightbeam Newsletter for TNFF: number 181; 1993 May. (box 3)
      Editor: Diane Miller.
    - Tightbeam Newsletter for TNFF: number 182; 1993 July. (box 3)
    - Tightbeam Newsletter for TNFF: number 184; 1993 November. (box 3)
    - Tightbeam Newsletter for TNFF: number 160; undated. (box 3)
    - Tightbeam Newsletter for TNFF: number 157; January. (box 3)
    - Tightbeam Newsletter for TNFF (8 issues): number unnumbered; undated. (box 3)
    - Title: number 15; 1973 June. (box 3)
      Editor: Donn Brazier.
    - Title: number 16; 1973 July. (box 3)
    - Title: number 17; 1973 August. (box 3)
    - Title: number 19; 1973 October. (box 3)
    - Title: number 29; 1973 August. (box 3)
    - Title: number 22; 1974 January. (box 3)
    - Title: number 23; 1974 February. (box 3)
    - Title: number 24; 1974 March. (box 3)
    - Title: number 25; 1974 April. (box 3)
    - Title: number 26; 1974 May. (box 3)
    - Title: number 27; 1974 June. (box 3)
    - Title: number 28; 1974 July. (box 3)
    - Title: number 30; 1974 July. (box 3)
    - Title: number 32; 1974 November. (box 3)
    - Title: number 44; 1975 November. (box 3)
    - Title: number 45; 1975 December. (box 3)
    - Title: number 46; 1976 January. (box 3)
    - Title: number 47; 1976 Feb. (box 3)
    - Title: number 48; 1976 March. (box 3)
    - Title: number 49; 1976 April. (box 3)
  - Tn - Tz
    - TNFF: volume 40, number 4; 1980 August. (box 4)
    - TNFF: volume 40, number 5; 1980 October. (box 4)
    - TNFF: volume 41, number 1; 1981 February. (box 4)
    - TNFF: volume 41, number 2; 1981 April. (box 4)
    - TNFF: volume 41, number 3; 1981 June. (box 4)
    - TNFF: volume 41, number 5; 1981 October. (box 4)
    - TNFF: volume 41, number 6; 1981 December. (box 4)
    - TNFF: volume 42, number 1; 1982 February. (box 4)
    - TNFF: volume 42, number 2; 1982 April. (box 4)
    - TNFF: volume 42, number 3; 1982 June. (box 4)
    - TNFF: volume 42, number 4; 1982 August. (box 4)
    - TNFF: volume 42, number 5; 1982 October. (box 4)
    - TNFF: volume 42, number 6; 1982 December. (box 4)
    - TNFF: volume 43, number 1; 1983 February. (box 4)
    - TNFF: volume 44, number 2; 1984 April. (box 4)
    - TNFF: volume 44, number 4; 1984 August. (box 4)
    - TNFF: volume 44, number 5; 1984 October. (box 4)
    - TNFF: volume 44, number 6; 1984 December. (box 4)
    - TNFF: volume 45, number 1; 1985 February. (box 4)
    - TNFF: volume 46, number 4; 1986 August. (box 4)
    - TNFF: volume 46, number 6; 1986 December. (box 4)
    - TNFF: volume 47, number 1; 1987 February. (box 4)
    - TNFF: volume 47, number 5; 1987 October. (box 4)
    - TNFF: volume 48, number 1; 1988 August. (box 4)
    - TNFF: volume 48, number 2; 1988 December. (box 4)
    - TNFF: volume 49, number 1; 1989 February. (box 4)
    - TNFF: volume 49, number 2; 1989 April. (box 4)
    - TNFF: volume 49, number 3; 1989 June. (box 4)
    - TNFF: volume 49, number 5; 1989 October. (box 4)
    - TNFF: volume 49, number 6; 1989 December. (box 4)
    - TNFF: volume 50, number 1; 1990 February. (box 4)
    - TNFF: volume 50, number 3; 1990 June. (box 4)
    - TNFF: volume 50, number 6; 1990 December. (box 4)
    - TNFF: volume 51, number 1; 1991 February. (box 4)
    - TNFF: volume 51, number 2; 1991 April. (box 4)
    - TNFF: volume 51, number 2; 1991 June. (box 4)
    - TNFF: volume 53, number 5; 1993 October. (box 4)
    - TNFF: volume 53, number 6; 1993 December. (box 4)
    - TNFF: volume 54, number 1; 1994 February. (box 4)
    - TNFF: volume 54, number 2; 1994 April. (box 4)
    - TNFF: volume 54, number 3; 1994 June. (box 4)
    - TNFF: volume 54, number 4; 1994 August. (box 4)
    - TNFF: volume 54, number 5; 1994 October. (box 4)
    - TNFF: volume 54, number 6; 1994 December. (box 4)
    - TNFF: volume 55, number 1; 1995 February. (box 4)
    - TNFF: volume 55, number 2; 1995 April. (box 4)
    - TNFF: volume 55, number 3; 1995 June. (box 4)
    - TNFF: volume 55, number 4; 1995 august. (box 4)
    - TNFF: volume 55, number 5; 1995 October. (box 4)
    - TNFF: volume 55, number 6; 1995 December. (box 4)
    - TNFF: volume 56, number 1; 1996 February. (box 4)
    - TNFF: volume 56, number 2; 1996 April. (box 4)
    - TNFF: volume 56, number 3; 1996 June. (box 4)
    - TNFF: volume 56, number 4; 1996 August. (box 4)
    - TNFF: volume 56, number 5; 1996 October. (box 4)
    - TNFF: volume 56, number 6; 1996 December. (box 4)
    - TNFF: volume 57, number 1; 1997 February. (box 4)
    - TNFF: volume 57, number 2; 1997 April. (box 4)
    - TNFF: volume 57, number 3; 1997 June. (box 4)
    - TNFF: volume 57, number 4; 1997 August. (box 4)
    - TNFF: volume 57, number 5; 1997 October. (box 4)
    - TNFF: volume 57, number 6; 1997 December. (box 4)
    - TNFF: volume 58, number 1; 1998 February. (box 4)
    - TNFF: volume 59, number 4; 1999 August. (box 4)
    - TNFF: volume 60, number 2 and 3; 2000 April/June. (box 4)
    - To The Stars: number 0; 1983. (box 3)
      Editor: Bo Trimble.
    - True Fan Adventure Theater: volume 1, number 8; 1973. (box 3)
      Editor: Anthony Isabella.
  - U - V
    - Univax and Unicorns: volume 1, number 1; 1975. (box 3)
      Editor: Melanie Solt.
    - Univax and Unicorns: volume 1, number 2; 1975. (box 3)
    - Univax and Unicorns: volume 1, number 3; 1975. (box 3)
    - Vertigo: number 18; 1973. (box 3)
      Editor: Edwin L Murray.
    - Vertigo: number 19; 1973. (box 3)
    - Vertigo: number 20; 1974. (box 3)
    - Vertigo: number 21; 1974. (box 3)
    - Vertigo: number 22; 1974. (box 3)
    - Vertigo: number 23; 1974. (box 3)
    - Vertigo: number 24; 1975. (box 3)
    - Vertigo: number 25; 1975. (box 3)
    - Vertigo: number 26; 1975. (box 3)
    - Vertigo: number 27; 1975. (box 3)
    - Vertigo: number 28; 1976. (box 3)
    - Vertigo: number 29; 1976. (box 3)
    - Vietnam: volume 1, number 1; 1988. (box 4)
      Editor: C. Brian Kelly.
  - W - X - Y - Z
    - Wahf-Full: number 8; 1982 March. (box 3)
      Editor: Jack R. Herman.
    - Wahf-Full: number 9; 1982 June. (box 3)
    - Wahf-Full: number 10; 1982 September. (box 3)
    - Wahf-Full: number 11; 1983 February. (box 3)
    - Wahf-Full: number 12; 1983 September. (box 3)
    - Wahf-Full: number 13; 1984 February. (box 3)
    - Wahf-Full: number 14; 1984 June-July. (box 3)
    - Wahf-Full: number 15.5; 1985 March-April. (box 3)
    - Warrior: volume 1, number 6; 1982 October. (box 4)
      Editor: Dez Skinn.
    - Weirdbook: number 14; 1979. (box 3)
    - Well of the Souls: number 5; 1986 January. (box 3)
      Editor: Sally Smith.
    - Whispers: volume 1, number 1; 1973 July. (box 3)
      Editor: Stuart Schiff.
    - White Wolf: number 1; 1986. (box 3)
      Editor: Stewart Wieck.
    - White Wolf: number 8; 1987 Dec/Jan. (box 3)
    - White Wolf: number 20; 1990 April-May. (box 3)
    - White Wolf: number 2; undated. (box 3)
    - White Wolf: number 3; undated. (box 3)
    - White Wolf: number 4; undated. (box 3)
    - White Wolf: number 5; undated. (box 3)
    - Witzend 13 (Good Girl Issue): number 13; 1985. (box 3)
      Editor: William Pearson.
    - Worlds of Fandom 29: number 29; 1973 August. (box 3)
    - Xenophilia: number 3; 1981 November. (box 3)
      Editor: Richard Faulder.
- II. Correspondence and related papers
  - Goodson, William Wilson, Jr. William Wilson Goodson Jr. correspondence, 1974-1987., 1 folder. (Box 3)
  - Fliers (printed matter) and catalogs., 1 folder. (Box 3)
  - Other fanzines., 1 folder. (Box 3)
  - Printed material from conventions., 2 folders. (Box 3)
  - Printed material from heroes conventions., 1 folder. (Box 3)